Guide to the Duke Mathematical Journal Records, 1924-1985 UA.24.27.0031
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Series, 1963-1972, bulk 1966-1971; 6
  - G (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - H (general) [1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - H (general) [2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - I-J (general), 1967-1970 (Box 12)
  - K (general), 1968-1972 (Box 12)
  - L (general), 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - Mc (general), 1965-1971 (Box 12)
  - M (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - N (general), 1969-1971 (Box 12)
  - O (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - P-Q (general), 1965-1971 (Box 12)
  - R (general), 1964-1971 (Box 12)
  - S-Sh (general), 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - Si-Sz (general) [1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - Si-Sz (general) [2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - T (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - U (general), 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - V (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - W-Wh (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - Wi-Wz (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1968-1970 (Box 12)
- Alphabetical Series, 1967-1974, bulk 1971-1974; 7
  - A (general), 1967-1973 (Box 13)
  - B (general) [1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - B (general) [2 of 2], 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - C (general), 1969-1974 (Box 13)
  - D (general), 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - Lynda Emerson, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - E (general), 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - F (general), 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - Fred Gehring, 1969-1974 (Box 13)
  - G (general), 1968-1974 (Box 13)
  - H (general) [1 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - H (general) [2 of 3], 1968-1973 (Box 13)
  - H (general) [3 of 3], 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - I (general), 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - J (general), 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - K (general), 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - L (general) [1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - L (general) [2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - Mc (general), 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - M (general), 1968-1974 (Box 13)
  - N (general), 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - O (general), 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Office Stuff, 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - P (general), 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - R (general), 1969-1973 (Box 13)
  - S-Sh (general), 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - Si-Sy (general), 1971-1974 (Box 13)
  - T (general), 1971-1974 (Box 13)
  - U (general), 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - V (general), 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - W-Wh (general), 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - Wi-Wy (general), 1970-1974 (Box 14)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1971-1973 (Box 14)
- Subject Files, 1949-1974; 8
  - American Mathematical Society et. al., 1971-1974 (Box 14)
  - Associate Editors before 1972, 1962-1969 (Box 14)
  - William Byrd Press, 1969-1974 (Box 14)
  - Editorial Board, 1949-1971 (Box 14)
  - Requests for Bound Copies of DMJ, 1956-1971 (Box 14)
  - Duke University Press, 1954-1971 (Box 14)
  - Subscriptions, Complimentary Copies, Postage, etc., 1947-1960 (Box 14)
  - Offprint Orders Sent to William Byrd Press, 1965-1971 (Box 14)
  - American Mathematical Society, 1952-1970 (Box 14)
  - Referee's Free Mailing List, 1957-1962 (Box 14)
  - Referees, 1960-1962 (Box 14)
  - Special Requests, Back Numbers, Exchanges, 1956-1971 (Box 14)
  - New Subscriptions (Inquries), 1955-1961 (Box 14)
  - William Byrd Press, 1966-1969 (Box 14)
  - William Byrd Press Bills, 1952-1971 (Box 14)
  - 1973 June (Box 14)
  - Associate Editors, 1972-1974 (Box 14)
  - Publication Charges, 1955-1962 (Box 14)
- Numerical Series, 1973-1974; 9
  - 390-499, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 506-522, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 533-548, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 553-574, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 575-599, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 603-625, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 626-649, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 650-669, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - 670-681, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
- Numerical Series, 1974-1982; 10
  - 740604-74191, 1974 March-September (Box 15)
  - 74203-74296, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - 74332-74491, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - 75020-75118, 1975 January-November (Box 15)
  - 75121-75232, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - 75250-75384, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - 75390-75502, 1975-1977 (Box 15)
  - 76014-76091, 1976 January-July (Box 15)
  - 76111-76241, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - 76242-76360, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - 76372-76524, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - 77030-77094, 1977 January-August (Box 15)
  - 77136-77330, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - 77332-77422, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - 77443-77520, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - 78011-78121, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - 78123-78254, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - 78255-78373, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - 78420-78473, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
  - 78481-78522, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - 79010-79173, 1979 January-November (Box 15)
  - 79191-79311, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - 79313-79420, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - 79425-79520, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
  - 80053-80171, 1980 January-September (Box 16)
  - 80172-80246, 1980 April-December (Box 16)
  - 80247-80313, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - 80331-80403, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - 80411-80491, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - 80491-80530, 1980-1982 (Box 16)
- Numerical Series, 1981-1988; 11
  - 101131-104061, 1981 January-September (Box 16)
  - 104200-106190, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - 107060-109250, 1981-1983 (Box 16)
  - 110050-111180, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - 112102-112231, 1981-1983 (Box 16)
  - 201110-202043, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - 202150-205172, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - 206020-207301, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - 208021-209132, 1982-1986 (Box 16)
  - 209202-211030, 1982-1984 (Box 16)
  - 211080-212021, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - 212110-212301, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - 301070-304180, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - 305022-307131, 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - 307190-308122, 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - 308230-312058, 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - 401050-403280, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - 403290-406040, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - 406080-409040, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - 409170-411121, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - 411231-412264, 1984-1987 (Box 17)
  - 501070-502112, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - 502132-504290, 1985-1987 (Box 17)
  - 504300-506250, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - 507160-510282, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - 511020-512280, 1985-1988 (Box 17)
- Misc. Correspondence, 1974-1985; 12
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1985 (Box 17)
- Record Books, 1951-1985; 13
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1951-1956 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1960-1964 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1964-1967 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1967-1971 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1971-1973 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1977-1979 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal Record of Papers in Process and Disposition, 1985 (Box 18)